Hi and welcome Fuxi again here on my channel. Nice to be here again. So fun to have you because today we have something to try on latex and leather harnesses and I'm hoping for your assistance. I will try my very best because I think it's fun.
So, Eileen Harness, send us some outfits.
Oh, there you go.
I'm done, I'm out.
Help! Please!
No, it's alright.
Um, you got the latex, I have the leather harnesses.
It's orange.
Orange and black. I like the combination of these colors.
Yeah, I think it's metallic black and the harness is dark gold.
Oh, it's the bodysuit.
Do you like orange?
I do.
Orange latex, yes?
Yeah, for sure.
It matches with my hair.
It does?
Of course.
Look.
Give a look.
Yeah, and this is the harness.
Gold and black.
Another orange outfit.
This one is nice.
It is metallic.
Yeah.
It's super shiny.
It's not that shiny because we didn't shine them.
We can do it like it.
Yeah.
What do you want to start with?
The orange one, I guess.
Okay, the latex. Then let's get changed.
Okay, we changed, but we're still not shiny.
Here you go. It's cold.
That's what I saw when the weather was warm.
Your turn.
We hoped for many flames but saw them turn to ash
We've been warned so many times and died so many more
Alright, so we've changed. Let's turn around.
What do you think? Do you like it?
It's super tight and I like the feeling of latex in general.
and this design is super unusual for me and give me some critical vibes but I kinda like it.
What would you?
Yeah, I think the cut is fun.
Fun. Super funny.
Super fun.
I like the cutouts here and also in the back. It's like, it reminds me of swimwear.
Yeah, kinda.
But I love that it fits so good.
Yeah.
Do you want to change?
I don't know.
Should we change?
The orange latex?
But I tried.
Orange too?
Yeah.
The small part.
Give it a try.
Come on.
No.
It will suit you.
Trust me.
Okay, we can change.
Yay.
Well, yeah.
We changed.
Obviously.
To be honest.
You don't look completely sold.
I like the first version.
Yeah.
Me too.
The change.
the change yeah i think this looked better on you and this look looks better with boobs to be honest
but i like i mean you can you can wear it too i like the like the cap but it looks better with
boobs but orange suits you it's the hair the hair always the hair but that's what you do i didn't
believe at first but yeah it works maybe because your skin is so white
as pale as possible you have to turn around once
now you
the bump looks great in it i like it i'd lie if i say it's comfortable
Yeah, this is very comfortable.
Yeah, that is.
I like it.
I think that's a cool design.
And it's, yeah.
But I think Elin Hans did a very good job there.
She did.
I like them.
But we have two more outfits.
Something completely different.
Bella, can you, do you want to show it or pick it up or what do you want?
I think this is the bra, I guess.
The panties, kind of.
I have something.
Oh, similar.
I guess.
So, yeah. Let's get changed.
Which one? I don't know.
Try first.
Try first. Do you want to change again?
Maybe. Let's see.
And we're back.
Last outfit. I love the combination.
With the mesh and the black.
Yeah, looks great.
I love these too. Thanks. I mean we're talking about the harnesses here. They're from Alien Harness. Harness obviously. Obviously. We put some catsuits underneath because we're on YouTube here and YouTube can be a little bit about policies concerning shiny or nakedness or whatever. We don't really know what YouTube likes or not.
So yeah, we made it YouTube safe and put on some fabric.
You should probably wear it without something.
Yeah, of course.
And I would wear it higher on my hip bones.
But the fabric is too slippery for this chain.
And yeah, I think it's smooth.
It will fit better on skin, directly.
Yeah, it will just stick to the skin better than to just fabric.
but I'm not that smooth. Not that soft. No, no. We're talking about the harnesses. Yes.
I really like the cut, the heart shape. Does it push like push-up bra a bit?
Not that much but it forms your breasts really nice. I like it. I like the
the gold. No, not the gold but the shape. Okay. The stripes. What I really like
about yours are the the cuts here in the bra part and the holes I mean without
fabric you would probably see... You look kind of sneaky! Really revealing!
It's a nice peek-a-boo situation. I like the chains on the sides I think it's cool
look with the chains here. I think I would prefer it in silver than in gold
because I usually wear silver jewelry.
You make up silver, you're...
Yeah, but the gold is really cool matched with your hair.
So right here, I think it looks better than with blue hair
because it's a more warm, warm, warm cold.
Warm color?
Warm color, warm cold.
Yeah.
Do you have the chain in the bag or a stripe?
I...
Oh.
I like it.
It's just leather, I guess.
Yeah.
It's leather too.
I like your bag. It's really cool. I like this kind of harnesses with the stripe in the middle.
Oh, like a racer. Oh, does it have like a racer back?
Yeah.
Nice. Nice one.
Okay.
So, be nice to me, maybe.
But I think we're done here.
Yeah, I think so.
Thanks for having me again. Thanks for joining. It's always fun, and I'm just not alone then. It's more fun
Someone to talk to. Yeah, someone to talk to. It's always great. Anyway, um, thanks for joining today. Check out Ilin Harness
I will link the shop down below in the description text. I will also link her socials
So you can check out our pages and yeah, just leave a thumbs up here, write a comment
what outfit was your favorite and I will see you next video maybe you too
hopefully. See you next time. Bye!